<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>./fix_it_felix_64.d64</path>
    <name>Fix It Felix Jr. 64</name>
    <image>./images/fix_it_felix_64-image.png</image>
    <video>./videos/fix_it_felix_64-video.mp4</video>
    <marquee>./fix_it_felix_64-marquee.png</marquee>
    <thumbnail>./images/fix_it_felix_64.png</thumbnail>
    <desc>Save Niceland from chaos! 
The inhabitants of this quiet place made a huge mistake when they decided to bulldoze Ralph's home in the forest to build an apartment block. Now he is raging and destroying everything around him! Fortunately, Ralph's arch enemy, Felix Jr., has to come to the rescue... He must use his magic hammer to repair all the windows that the giant keeps breaking!

Unfortunately, climbing a tall building is hard enough without an angry villain attacking you! The brave protagonist of this story needs your help...Give him a hand to fix everyone's windows and put a stop to the mayhem going on in town!

However, no noble mission is easy to accomplish! The intimidating Wreck-It Ralph is waiting for you at the top story of each level. He will throw bricks at you and try to stop you from repairing the building. What is more, you need to watch out for unexpected obstacles during your ascent... Even ducks can make you lose a precious life!

The game consists of multiple levels, where you find yourself at the bottom part of the screen, while Ralph is above you, throwing bricks around in rage. Your mission is to fix all the windows in sight without falling off.

What is more, you need to make sure you don't run out of time! Check on how much time you have remaining by keeping an eye on the timer clock at the top of the screen. Here you can also see your current score and how many lives you can count on. Make sure to move swiftly and carefully! Once you lose all your four lives, you have to start the game from the very beginning!

Thankfully, the citizens of Niceland love Fix-It Felix Jr.! You will see them pop up in their window from time to time, leaving a piping hot apple pie for you. Yum! Pick it up as fast as you can, as it will give you extra points, invincibility for a short time, plus the ability to smash through bricks, piles, and even teach those pesky ducks a lesson. Teach two ducks a lesson while high on pie to triple the score, that's the cherry on the top! You'll need all the points that you can score, as you'll get an extra life every 20,000.
    </desc>
    <rating>1</rating>
    <releasedate>20200426T000000</releasedate>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <developer>Antonio Savona, Steven Day, Saul Cross</developer>
    <md5>67cbd1c50d9de68dec6b20c33b63b135</md5>
    <lang>en</lang>
  </game>
</gameList>
