<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>./Reflectron (aetherbyte).pce</path>
    <name>Reflectron</name>
    <desc>You are a Biological Entity Remover Node And Repair Droid (or B.E.R.N.A.R.D. for short), working for the evil robot overlord on his deadly mobile space station. Charged with maintaining the primary laser cannon, B.E.R.N.A.R.D has, however, developed something of a conscience. Instead, he has chosen to defy his master and do his best to stop the cannon's DELTA CRYSTAL from charging up by destroying the MEGA PROTONS with his cranial gun. Will he be able to stop the cannon from decimating another innocent world?</desc>
    <image>./images/Reflectron (aetherbyte)-image.png</image>
    <video>./videos/Reflectron (aetherbyte)-video.mp4</video>
    <marquee>./images/Reflectron (aetherbyte)-marquee.png</marquee>
    <thumbnail>./images/Reflectron (aetherbyte)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
    <developer>Andrew Darovich</developer>
    <publisher>Aetherbyte</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <crc32>6A3727E2</crc32>
    <md5>40540be45e4f802344cfcb9f43b527b0</md5>
    <lang>jp</lang>
    <region>jp</region>
    <cheevosHash>40540BE45E4F802344CFCB9F43B527B0</cheevosHash>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Santatlantean (aetherbyte).pce</path>
    <name>Santatlantean</name>
    <desc>Jealous of all the time her husband spends drinking sherry and eating biscuits in other people's houses, Mrs Claus decides the only way to be rid of her overweight husband is to put an evil spell on the Christmas decorations and let them do the dirty work for her. As Santa, you must destroy these festive fiends, but beware; evil baubles are lying in wait, candy canes attack without warning and scented candles are out to burn your beard off!

Santatlantean is a festive high-score action shoot 'em up (based on Aetherbyte's Atlantean) which is free to download and play on a PC Engine emulator of your choice (such as Magic Engine, Mednafen or Ootake) or flash card.</desc>
    <image>./images/Santatlantean (aetherbyte)-image.png</image>
    <video>./videos/Santatlantean (aetherbyte)-video.mp4</video>
    <marquee>./images/Santatlantean (aetherbyte)-marquee.png</marquee>
    <thumbnail>./images/Santatlantean (aetherbyte)-thumb.png</thumbnail>
    <developer>Andrew Darovich</developer>
    <publisher>Aetherbyte</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <crc32>E6B38AF1</crc32>
    <md5>37f4ae5a1c9d4b02b441d075c6474a5b</md5>
    <lang>jp</lang>
    <region>jp</region>
    <cheevosHash>12C9CB92855185A15B315435EC8EADF7</cheevosHash>
  </game>
</gameList>
